<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Marc Bouriot</title><link>https://example.org/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Marc Bouriot</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://example.org/posts/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:00:00 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/getting-started/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This post will guide you in setting up your very own Hugo site with this theme. It covers the essential parts: &lt;a href="#Installation"&gt;installation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="#usage"&gt;basic usage&lt;/a&gt; and recommended &lt;a href="#next-steps"&gt;next steps&lt;/a&gt;. After setting up the basics, feel free to also take a look at other &lt;a href="https://example.org/posts/"&gt;posts&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="installation"&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This guide is a shorter version of &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/getting-started/quick-start/"&gt;Hugo&amp;rsquo;s quick start&lt;/a&gt; (you may even say it&amp;rsquo;s a quicker start). If you face any problems or want more comprehensive content, make sure to check it out!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://example.org/posts/configuration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:00:00 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/configuration/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This page outlines the configuration options for the theme. There are plenty of settings for tweaking your site&amp;rsquo;s layout and content presentation. Key features include options for controlling the side pane visibility, adjusting the number of items displayed on each list page, and managing elements such as featured posts, recent posts, taxonomies, and related content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="global-config"&gt;Global Config&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following configuration options can be added to your site&amp;rsquo;s Hugo config file.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Les technologies émergentes</title><link>https://example.org/posts/article-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:00:00 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/article-1/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;En 2025, les technologies émergentes amènent l’UX/UI vers des expériences plus contextuelles et intelligentes. La réalité augmentée et l’UX prédictif obligent à penser des systèmes d’interaction à la place de simples écrans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="réalité-augmentée--linterface-dans-lespace"&gt;Réalité augmentée : l’interface dans l’espace&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;La réalité augmentée ne se limite plus au e‑commerce : elle enrichit désormais des lieux culturels, éducatifs ou médicaux. Dans une visite comme celle du Mémorial de Waterloo, les utilisateurs superposent les scènes historiques, les flèches de navigation et annotations à l’environnement réel, ce qui transforme la visite en une histoire interactif tout en ajoutant contraste, taille de texte et audiodescription pour rester accessible aux publics malvoyants.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Showcase</title><link>https://example.org/posts/showcase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:00:00 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/posts/showcase/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This page focuses on what you can do in terms of markdown syntax. Here you can see which and how each of the components are rendered to HTML in terms of structure and styling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="the-use-of-headings"&gt;The use of Headings&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Headings are larger text intended for section titles, and they vary in size from 1 to 5 (bigger to smaller) as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="heading-1"&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="heading-2"&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="heading-3"&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id="heading-4"&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h6 id="heading-5"&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h2 id="paragraphs"&gt;Paragraphs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paragraphs are containers for standard page content. Its font is defined and configurable via CSS as mentioned in &lt;a href="https://example.org/features/customization"&gt;customization&lt;/a&gt; post.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>